<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><srw_dc:dc xmlns:srw_dc="info:srw/schema/1/dc-schema" xmlns="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="info:srw/schema/1/dc-schema http://www.loc.gov/z3950/agency/zing/srw/dc-schema.xsd"><title>Comparative Central European Holocaust studies /</title><creator>Vasvári, Louise O. (Louise Olga), 1943-</creator><creator>Tötösy de Zepetnek, Steven, 1950-</creator><type>text</type><publisher>[West Lafayette, IN] : Purdue University Press,</publisher><date>c2008.</date><language>eng</language><description>Includes bibliographical references and index.</description><description>Representations of Budapest 1944-1945 in Holocaust literature / Ruth G. Biro -- The Holocaust as a paradigm for ethical thinking and representation / Tamas Kisantal -- About antisemitism in post-1989 Hungary / Magdalena Marsovszky -- About the narratives of a blood libel case in post-Shoah Hungary / Andrea Peto -- Mapping the lines of fact and fiction in Holocaust testimonial novels / Anna Richardson -- Rescue narratives by Central European Holocaust survivors from Carpatho-Russia / Ilana Rosen -- The Third Reich and the Holocaust in East German official memory / Anne Rothe -- On the Serbian translation of Kertesz's Sorstalansag (Fatelessness) / Marko Cudic -- Kertesz and the problem of guilt in unfinished mourning / Esther Faye - Polyphony in Kertesz's Kaddish a meg nem szuletett gyermekert (Kaddish for an Unborn Child) / Sandor Radnoti -- Arendt and Kertesz on the banality of evil / Mihaly Szilagyi-Gal -- Towards a new reading of Fink's The Journey / Iris Milner -- Emigree Central European women's Holocaust life writing / Louise O. Vasvari -- Introduction to and bibliography of Central European women's Holocaust life writing in English / Louise O. Vasvari.</description><subject>Kertész, Imre, 1929---Criticism and interpretation.</subject><subject>Jews--Persecutions--Europe, Central--History.</subject><subject>Jews--Persecutions--Hungary--History.</subject><subject>Holocaust, Jewish (1939-1945)--Europe, Central--History.</subject><subject>Holocaust, Jewish (1939-1945)--Hungary--History.</subject><coverage>Europe, Central--Ethnic relations.</coverage><coverage>Hungary--Ethnic relations.</coverage><identifier>URN:ISBN:9781557535269</identifier></srw_dc:dc>